<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="message"> A smart home or automated home could be based on a platform or hubs that control smart devices and appliances.
        [26] For instance, using Apples HomeKit, manufacturers can have their home products and accessories controlled by an application in
        iOS devices such as the iPhone and the Apple Watch.[27][28] This could be a dedicated app or iOS native applications such as Siri.
        This can be demonstrated in the case of Lenovos Smart Home Essentials, which is a line of smart home devices that are controlled
        through Apples Home app or Siri without the need for a Wi-Fi bridge.[29] www.stackoverflow.com There are also dedicated smart home
        hubs that are offered as standalone platforms to connect different smart home products and these include the Amazon Echo, Google Home,
        Apples HomePod, and Samsungs SmartThings Hub.[30] In addition to the commercial systems, there are many non-proprietary, open source ecosystems;
        including Home Assistant, OpenHAB and Domoticz.oT devices can be used to enable remote health monitoring and emergency notification systems.
        These health monitoring devices can range from blood pressure and heart rate monitors to advanced devices capable of monitoring specialized implants
        such as pacemakers, Fitbit electronic wristbands, or advanced hearing aids.[43] Some hospitals have begun implementing smart beds that can detect
        when they are occupied and when a patient is attempting to get up. It can also adjust itself to ensure appropriate pressure and support is applied to
        the patient without the manual interaction of nurses. A 2015 Goldman Sachs report indicated that healthcare IoT devices can save the United States
        more than $300 billion in annual healthcare expenditures by increasing revenue and decreasing cost.[44] Moreover, the use of mobile devices to support
        medical follow-up led to the creation of m-health, used analyzed health statistics.

Specialized sensors can also be equipped within living spaces to monitor the health and general well-being of senior citizens,
        while also ensuring that proper treatment is being administered and assisting people regain lost mobility via therapy as well.
        These sensors create a network of intelligent sensors that are able to collect, process, transfer, and analyze valuable information
        in different environments, such as connecting in-home monitoring devices to hospital-based systems.[41] Other consumer devices to encourage
        healthy living, such as connected scales or wearable heart monitors, are also a possibility with the IoT.[47] End-to-end health monitoring IoT
        platforms are also available for antenatal and chronic patients, helping one manage health vitals and recurring medication requirements.

Advances in plastic and fabric electronics fabrication methods have enabled ultra-low cost, use-and-throw IoMT sensors. These sensors, along with
        the required RFID electronics, can be fabricated on paper or e-textiles for wireless powered disposable sensing devices.
        Applications have been established for point-of-care medical diagnostics, where portability and low system-complexity is essential.

As of 2018 IoMT was not only being applied in the clinical laboratory industry,[38] but also in the healthcare and health insurance industries.
        IoMT in the healthcare industry is now permitting doctors, patients, and others, such as guardians of patients, nurses, families, and similar,
        to be part of a system, where patient records are saved in a database, allowing doctors and the rest of the medical staff to have access to patient
        information.[51] Moreover, IoT-based systems are patient-centered, which involves being flexible to the patients medical conditions.[citation needed]
        IoMT in the insurance industry provides access to better and new types of dynamic information. This includes sensor-based solutions such as biosensors,
        wearables, connected health devices, and mobile apps to track customer behaviour. This can lead to more accurate underwriting and new pricing modelsaaaa
        aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
        aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaabbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbcccccccccccccc
        cccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccccdddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddd
        dddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddddeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
        eeeeeeeeeeeffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggg
        gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggghhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiijjjjjj
        jjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkklllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
        lmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooppppppppppppppppppppppppp
        pppppppppppppppp</string>
</resources>